from west cliff colorado which is one of
the most beautiful little communities
i've ever been in
and
he's now moving into the dome
so that sounds like a really neat
project he's been speaking at these
conferences now for a few years he
started studying what he calls weird
science in
college at the age of 12.
and about 67 years ago he started
actually applying what he'd been
studying he's been
branching into
every field including alchemy and
linguistics he said he has a little bit
about linguistics for us today and then
he has a vision for the future to make
this world a great place for
all the children and everybody coming up
and i think that's pretty neat because i
share that vision
he also
has invented a chair for
sage's
little sister sage is here with us too
and she's his daughter
and you can wave if you want
and
her little sister has cerebral palsy so
he's finding that
some of this stuff has very direct
application in his family so here's
vernon roth
[Applause]
well this uh this conference is turning
out to be really neat really uh
interesting
so
we're going to
move we got a lot of information to
cover and talk about if anybody has any
questions just shout it out and
anything if i move too fast just ask any
questions you need to and i'll try and
cover it as quickly as possible but we
have a lot to go over
so
this year has been has been very very
interesting and um
in the research aspect and everything
that that that my family and the people
that i've been working with have been uh
have been discovering i've been back and
forth across the country i have uh
i have been north and south back and
forth and seen seen many many amazing
things and experienced many amazing
things so we're going to be talking a
lot about that on today
so
oh there's a laser
wonderful
all right
so to start out
uh-oh
the left button
okay to start out we have a little quote
here
and i want people to be thinking about
certain things as we as we go into this
as we go into this presentation today
this is a quote from a hundred years ago
and it's absolutely applicable at this
point in time since today's scientists
have substituted mathematics for
experiments and they wander off through
equation after equation and eventually
build a structure which has no relation
to reality
so
so what this means is
that you can you can create formulations
all day long that says
this is the nature of reality or that is
the nature of reality
but
none of it actually stands up none of it
actually works until you apply it to
our physical reality
now this isn't just this isn't just a
weird science uh weird science
phenomenon
because i was actually studying a
mechanical motions book and then the
very very first preface it shows a a a
it postulates a problem to you
and this is a problem of
two pulleys
two ropes and a weight
and so the pulleys the ropes are
assuming the the weights say to the
pulleys it says i want to move i want to
go someplace
and so they get their two ropes involved
and they loop themselves up and over the
pulleys and they want to try and figure
out exactly how much weight is going to
be on this rope and how much weight is
going to be on this rope if the two
pulleys are offset and no different
sizes and such
and in conventional science there is no
formula to calculate this out there is
no way to theoretically
figure out
how much weight is going to be where it
has to be done experimentally
and this is conventional science saying
yes we can't figure out a simple
mechanical motion
we have to actually
do it in physical reality
so i want you to remember that as we go
along here today and as we as we uh as
we examine the future as we examine
these technologies because
you have to you actually have to get
down and do it
there is
there's all these mechanical or
something all these equations that say
energy cannot be pulled from magnets
but as you're going to be seeing today
energy can be pulled from magnets
and it's been it's it's not new it's
been around for
50 60 700 years it's been dreamed of for
for thousands of years so maybe they had
it too we will see
as we move on that by the way was nikola
tesla
and uh he was using it like i said a
hundred years ago and it's just as
applicable today
and we're not moving anywhere
where's the device i'm controlling here
oh there we go
okay
last year i said some things that should
have thrown off a lot of red flags
and first of all one of those things was
talking about the crystalline structure
of a material crystalline structure
dictates whether or not a material is
going to be a magnetic
paramagnetic
diamagnetic
is it does it have conductivity
is it superconductive is it
semi-conductive
does it deflect magnetism does it absorb
magnetism
does it transmit electric electricity
does it absorb radiation does it negate
radiation all of these things can be
done with conventional materials
but it is entirely dependent upon the
crystal and geometrical structure of the
material
so
if you want to
do you think that would be a an
applicable thing to a magnetic motor
there are there are magnets are there
are materials that deflect magnets
90 degree 90 are certainly not not
magnets but deflect magnetism at a 90
degree angle there are materials that
absorb magnetism you put that over a 10
000 gauss magnetic field you'll have zip
on the other side it's kind of dangerous
and we'll get into that but that's okay
there's also
materials that
emit of course they emit radiation but
there's also materials that negate
radiation it all has to do with crystal
and geometrical structure of the
material
so
what we're going to do is we're going to
we're going to examine that
now
think about that as we're as we're going
in today and we're going to talk about a
little bit about ether and how this
applies to magnetism and how this
applies to energy
so first off how many people believe
that ether or one of its
uh one of its various incarnations
exists raise your hand
okay
everybody here just about everybody here
believes that ether or one of its
various incarnations exists yes
absolutely there it is
we need a magic marker we'll just put a
little a in front of that e and we'll be
fine right
wrong way
okay
the reason
why it's been very very difficult to
to uh prove with conventional science
the existence of ether
is because there it's very difficult to
find a differential in the ether we
we're going to get into that but let's
imagine that if that if you were a fish
living at the bottom of the ocean
swimming along in the water
philosophical question says is the fish
even aware of the water
or is it just the medium that it is used
to moving through
okay so we are the fish at the bottom of
the intergalactic fish bowl
moving through a substance and we've
been talking about it etheric gas the
different the various different
incarnations or labels that we like to
put things put on things because as
human beings we have a very difficult
time with anything we can't quantify
qualify and easily cross-reference
so
we're going to talk a little bit about
differentials because it is absolutely
essential to finding ether and
experiencing ether and utilizing ether
first of all we're going to talk about
conventional differentials
wind if i'm standing here
stationary and the wind is blowing past
me at 60 miles an hour there's a
differential there
and i can have power i can find power
because there's a differential from my
position as stationary and the 60 mile
per hour wind is going past if i'm
running at 60 miles an hour
then there's there's real no really no
differential between me and the wind i
can't get energy from that spot
water flowing water you have a
stationary stationary object you have
water flowing across it you have a
differential in the way and that is the
way you gather energy
temperature
until recently it's been very difficult
to get
to get power from a temperature
differential with the development of
better and better thermocouples better
and better for instance peltier
junctions um
this is uh this is becoming more and
more applicable
i just recently uh
saw pictures of a house in tokyo japan
it's five stories tall
it runs entirely upon its own power
and that is done all with temperature
differentials super efficient
thermocouples that allow
allow amazing power from very very
slight temperature degree changes
so at night you have temperature out you
have a higher
excuse me higher temperature inside and
a lower temperature outside you have a
temperature differential and vice versa
during the day and this thing generates
its own power in the neighborhood of 30
kilowatts
so
sunlight of course is the other is
another differential we have light
coming at us over here we have no light
we have a differential we can we can get
get power there and of course there is
the electrical circuits
we'll talk about that a little bit later
now the unconventional differentials
are our magnetism
magnetism we have an automatic
differential we have north we have south
well i'll get into more about that
because that's actually a fallacy we
just like to call it those
but that is a differential and we can
get power from that
etheric accumulators if you have
a
certain amount of energy etheric energy
out here and you have a very powerful
etheric energy here you have a
differential and you can create power
there
certain shapes and patterns documented
by dan davidson
will create differentials as well and
their three-dimensional equivalents
are wonderful little
little geometrical patterns here those
all create differentials of etheric
energy and if we learn how to tie into
those we can have as much power as we
want
incidentally this is also how we
experience our physical world okay
you cannot experience the world without
a differential
if i am the fish in the ocean
and it is completely black i can't see
anything there must be shades if it's
completely light i can't see anything
either there has to be shades this is
how we differentiate our physical
reality my hand is moving through the
air and suddenly it hits something the
differential tells me that it's there
this is how we measure magnetism how we
measure light how we measure electricity
so think about these things when you
start to look at it this way you start
to realize that there is free energy all
around us
so moving right along
we're going to talk about
etheric light and
which which is my favorite uh which is
my favorite
uh label to put on ether energy and
we're gonna be talking about geometrical
structures when i talked last year i
said that
everything comes down to geometrical
patterns what type of geometrical
pattern is in the crystalline structure
of the material and so we have
these beautiful geometrical patterns all
of the gold ones up here are the
platonic solids plato said that all
nature all materials are divided up into
different geometrical patterns at their
center at their core and we found that
this is absolutely true this by the way
is the
geometrical pattern of gold
and i'll show a picture of it later on
but this is also the geometrical pattern
esoterically that would say
life rejuvenation and all that fun stuff
later on
the geometrical patterns become the
archimedean solids which are the
platonic solids melded into other shapes
and forms and how you put these forms
together dictates what you have oh i
forgot to mention it i'm not just
talking off my hat here okay
there are three genius guys who woke up
one day and said hey i want to know why
this material this little piece of steel
or this little piece of copper will
conduct electricity versus that cloth
or that piece of plastic will not and so
they set about figuring this whole thing
out
and eventually they got the nobel prize
for it for this research because they
were able to make plastic
plastic
that is able to conduct electricity many
many times better than
metals
you can conduct electricity without a
magnetic field how's that that's
interesting
and they did it all by structuring the
material with crystalline forms got the
nobel prize for it they deserved it it's
fantastic research so this is actually
being backed up by
conventional scientific
research
all right so
excuse me when we start to infuse
etheric energy into different crystal
and geometrical patterns we get
we get different types of energy out of
it all right when when
etheric energy is imploded well i'm
getting ahead of myself there sorry
when you structure the geometrical
pattern or some of the energy into
patterns you get you get different types
of energy out of it
all energy is born out of the ether this
was
this was said a hundred years ago it's
being said now in conventional physics
they just say it a different way light
magnetism everything is born out of the
ether without it we don't exist
if you were to remove all of the energy
from us from any given location
all life in there ceases to exist which
is actually documented by people that
have removed all magnetism from certain
areas and everything in it dies
so we're gonna
move along move right along here very
quickly we're gonna say what is the
magnitude or what is the mechanism that
allows ether to become energy and that
mechanism
is implosion
the mechanism is implosion and that is
what allows us to take ether
and condense it down into either energy
or physical reality or all of the
various incarnations between because not
everything is is is uh completely
physical or completely etheric or um or
energetic there are various stages in
between
here's another one
so what is implosion
etheric implosion
is an internal and etheric implosion is
an internal repeating pattern the when
it encounters itself it generates an an
external field
so
if we have a pattern right here
and we were to charge this with etheric
energy
would be there it'd be cool i mean on a
subatomic level wherever whatever level
it is it's charged with etheric energy
as soon as it meets itself
then it generates an external field how
it meets itself dictates what types of
external fields it generates
so to say that another way
etheric light implodes into a
geometrical shape creating a
self-repeating fractal
this is what we measure as all the
various incarnations of energy
so if you ram enough etheric energy into
a single location and it's a single
geometrical pattern
there's a button right there and it's a
single geometrical pattern
what do you get you get a radioactive
material we've done it
turned uh turned a steel rod
using nothing but an etheric imploder
into a highly alf
a highly charged alpha source
you can you can make it go away it's a
little bit more difficult to make it go
away but
this is what happens when what's that
okay
so
when we when you are able to charge the
energy when you're able to charge the
energy into a crystalline pattern you
get different things this is what
happens in conventional magnetism
we have a we have a uh
we have a coil we put in our little
pieces of neodymium that isn't charged
yet we
pound a whole bunch of joules of energy
into it and boom you've got yourself a
magnet what are the the the strongest
magnets now are up to what uh
83 pounds per square inch something like
that i i don't remember exactly what it
is we pulled pulled
straight across with this technique
with this understanding
we've actually done in the lab
we've actually gotten not
neodymium not these rare earth exotic
materials we've gotten pure steel up to
20 to 87 pounds per square inch
so
and the interesting thing is if you were
to take two neodymium magnets
like these right here you take two
neodymium magnets and start to heat them
up they're going to lose their magnetism
very very quickly
that steel is going to hold its
magnetism until it's melting apart
so the applications for that are
tremendous
anybody seeing applications for that
okay
i like audience participation if i if if
i make sense tell me if i don't make
sense
throw something
[Music]
in that situation listen one thing that
he he said kiri's law is no no longer
fell in that situation here's the deal
when i went into physics studying
physics
with dr with professor gilbert he just
passed away recently um he said
something interesting he said
there is no law there is no real law
this is all a story this is all a
creation of people that have that have
decided that this this works for right
here
okay but what about right over there
does it work over there
does it work over there if you don't
like the story go out and write your own
do it all over again
whatever these these are these are what
i'm going to be talking about today
these are these are techniques that you
can use to explore the reality but
reality isn't a law
reality is a is a is amazing changing
and dynamic force
so
laws ah you know what
they work in one way they don't work in
another way we worked with newtonian
physics then we went to einsteinian
physics well in the interim we went to
ether physics and now we're going to
quantum physics and wave theory and all
these different theories
don't get stuck in a law
if you don't like it rewrite it that's
what it's for right
that's what the laws of a country are
for you don't like it okay we'll change
it we'll figure it out
okay i skipped over this
um oops
can we go back real quick
thank you
i skipped over the the gold structure of
the uh the cubic gold structure which is
very interesting because there are
several other elements that are also
cubes
and they are just lacking an essential
holographic uh
a possibility of an atom in the center
or something not an atom but an electron
in the center and if you were to infuse
it with a fuse those other
elements with enough electricity or
enough energy you would then make gold
oh this is actually you know i'll wait
until the end of that somebody remind me
about that later okay you know don't
worry don't we don't need to go back
all right moving right along
we're going to be examining magnets now
we've got these cool little neodymium
magnets here
and
one thing i've noticed when when people
are
working with magnetic motors and i've
seen a bunch of them
we're taught that magnets
are these little cool little static
things now how many people here have
been taught that magnet is a static
a static unit it has a set field
everybody raise your hand if you've been
taught that magnet is a static thing all
right about uh there's half
or so
that is that is not a reality the
beautiful little
patterns that come when you put a magnet
under a set of iron filings
is what happens when you line up a whole
bunch of microscopic
magnets together and you allow them to
take whatever shape you want this is a
static field
magnets are not static at all
they are not static they move they are
very dynamic they flow
okay that's what happens when you stack
up a bunch of tiny magnets together as
they take that shape now that's a shape
that we can work with but it's not the
true nature of a magnet
it is a fake it is a um
it uh it's not reality
so we're going to we're going to uh
i need some audience participation sage
would you come up here please
let me do something real quick this is a
uh
this is what's called a tri-field meter
it measures electromagnetic fields
magnetic fields you see that you have to
get this magnet very close to the
meter in order to deflect it i'm hoping
you can see that out there oops there we
go
we have to get it very close to the
meter in order to deflect it
and as soon as we
this is a little thing i took the fan
off of a off of a little electric motor
fan you cannot you can definitely not
measure
yeah that would be great if you could
set it down right there we could use
that at the the tube too the tube
john john the tube too please
yeah you notice that it's not deflecting
through her body at all
but we're going to just turn on that
and suddenly
oops
sorry about that
there we go sorry sweetie
um did everybody see that
as soon as the magnet
you can't put it back on
okay as soon as the magnet starts to
spin
it starts to deflect now how many
magnetic motors have you seen
that are that that are that the magnets
all turn on on a rotating shaft or on a
on on a disc or a flywheel and then
right outside of that they got
themselves a a magnetic shell a housing
maybe some bars holding it in place
okay if you build a magnet or assuming
if you build a motor to work on a static
magnet
and as soon as you start moving it it's
not going to do anything
because the entire dynamic of the magnet
has changed at that point
all right now mapping that mapping where
that changes where those changes occur
thank you sweetie you can sit down uh
mac being where those changes occur
that's going to be a very complex task
but we have some we have some help with
that
next thing now everybody's seen it but
i've got to do it on film um
we've got a piece of metal here that
does not well there's some strange uh
there's some strange reactions when you
get it close but you drop this thing
you drop this through
and it takes a very long time to fall
through because
everything in the universe is either
magnetic
diamagnetic or paramagnetic now before
we got our beautiful little uh
periodic table of elements it has
hydrogen over here and it goes down and
got the radioactive elements down here
before they put that all together there
was a much more intuitive table of
elements and that started out with
the magnetic materials here
the paramagnetic materials here
and the diamagnetic materials over here
and you know what connected these things
the noble gases
connected them all
and you know what
alchemical research which is not
actually labeled alchemical research is
now showing is that to change one to the
other to the other
it requires an implosion and noble gases
so
moving right along oh and and uh oh i'll
get to that later
okay so
that was the uh that was the older
periodic table at uh the in use about
1920s somewhere around there
yes
you can have all my notes after we're
done
all right
anyway um
here we go
oh we just did our magnetic experiment
so we're ready to move on oh oh i got
one more for you anybody seen on the uh
anybody seen on the uh youtube or
anywhere they see the the experiment
where you put an electrolyzer into water
and you're bubbling the hydrogen and
oxygen off and you put a magnet
underneath it and it starts to swirl
i mean look that up sometimes swirling
magnetic fields is very very very uh
illuminating so we're not draining the
magnet but it's actually causing a a
change in the physical reality of those
uh hydrogen oxygen bubbles coming off
well there's an interesting fellow by
the name of
eckhart
i'm sorry it slipped my mind i believe
it's eckhart did some experiments
way back when they got hydrogen out of
um out of water by putting an iron bar
into a vessel that's filled with a 10
sulfuric acid solution and they get
hydrogen off this is what they used to
power the street lamps with in
in new york they'd get hydrogen they
filled bubbles with or filled balloons
with this with this stuff coming off
there
so he said he wanted to see what would
happen if he put a very very powerful
horseshoe magnet around this around this
bar
and so he did this he set it up he
actually had two bars set up in a glass
tube and he put a very powerful
horseshoe magnet on this on these bars
and you know what happened he he
suddenly found that he was not just
getting hydrogen he was suddenly getting
oxygen as well
oh wait a minute here we have a
completely passive device
a a horseshoe magnet
generating electricity because that's
the only way you're going to get oxygen
off of a off of a bar in a situation
like that is if you've got if you've
actually got an electrical current
flowing back and forth so he's got an
electrical current flowing from a
horseshoe magnet so he did all sorts of
experiments he hooked up wires
completely shorted the whole system out
and it was still bubbling oxygen off of
this off of the solution
um
what was very interesting about this was
i mean that's cool we know that
we know that magnetism can generate an
electrical field we know that but here's
the here's the here's the real kicker
and this is the question that's gonna
that i want you guys to to to think
about this and have nightmares about
and that is that
the magnet
died
the magnet lost 10 percent of its power
every 24 hours
all it's doing is energizing an iron bar
it can sit there and do that for a
thousand years but under this condition
it died now why is that
think about that as we go on
okay
um how many people want to see something
that that uh that will actually help
them to understand true magnetism
could we click play on that i think you
just have to click it
thank you
it's not working
huh
is there a video yeah that's a video
anyway
what you're about to see is a actual
real-time footage of a neodymium magnet
and it is about it it's about this size
north and south you need your thumb
drive
yeah
ow
thank
you thanks sweetie
there you go i'll get it i'll get it
later
yeah there you go
let's go put this over here
where it's safe
all right
what we're going to be seeing here is an
actual
real-time footage
of a magnetic field as it flows and this
is north and this is south and we're
hoping that it's actually going to work
because it's really fantastic
this is a true magnetic field this is
not the iron filings that you saw
stacked up on top of each other this
defies that
it's not working is it
what's that
no it's not
i i cannot tell you how it's done i'm
sorry
but um if you want to experiment
great go for it
but i am i cannot tell you how it's done
anyway what you what you will see here
is two counter rotating vortexes of
energy they are in constant motion they
never stop the magnets just keep on
going and every once in a while you'll
see one disappear off there and another
one come in from the side and they'll
just keep on flowing and keep on flowing
and they never stop
so these this my friends is the
really the motor of the universe it
never ends it keeps on going forever and
ever
and so
um what are those particles now that's
that's that's an amazing question i'm
going to tell you tell you a little
story while uh while we're working here
and i'm i'm hoping i don't get in
trouble for this but um a friend of mine
takes a very powerful big neodymium
magnet
and he puts a
suction a glass section on one side and
draws a hard vacuum on it puts a glass
section on the other side and draws
another hard vacuum on it then puts the
whole thing into a vacuum chamber and
draws a hard vacuum on it right and they
they they x-rayed the x-ray
spectrographed it out there's nothing
there there's nothing inside that hard
vacuum
and so they leave it and they come back
a month later and there's still nothing
there
all right there we are there we're going
see this is real-time footage
of the magnetic fields they're not being
stimulated by anything nothing external
is coming in that is the magnetic field
right there that is the reality of a
magnetic field
there's a little bit more to it than
this but that's enough for right now now
you remember i said that everything is
either diamagnetic paramagnetic
or magnetic
the magnet is right down here
running horizontal
so the magnet is being held
you know right there okay and it's just
a little magnet this is this was uh
uh this was about an inch inch long
magnet
so here we have this magnetic field now
if you've ever played with magnetism and
you try and try and stick something to
stick something to a very powerful
magnet and bring a needle in or a nail
or something like that in here it's
going to automatically jump to this side
right it's going to jump to this side
you can't stick stick a piece of metal a
small enough piece of metal right here
because there's no magnetic field right
there
you know what will stick there
a piece of diamagnetic material
because there is a different field
associated with diamagnetism
than magnetism diamagnetics highly
unexplored but there's a field
associated with with it and it will
stick at that point maybe put a sphere
magnet there too and that'll generate
enough of a field that it wants to
balance itself out in this nice little
triangle pattern here but anyway this is
the true nature of magnetism
this is the way it moves thank you john
i really appreciate that this is the way
it moves it continually rotates in
counter-rotating fields now here's the
kicker
we're going to move on this is just one
set of fields
in a magnet wait a minute we were told
we got a north and we got a south that's
it right
yes
is it always slow like that
um it moves faster for for stronger
magnets um the the medium that we were
using there kind of slowed it down so we
could actually see it
so it was very very quickly oh thank you
i
moved right on the head this is the true
nature of a magnetic field this spider
web here
this is what we call north
these are what we the the red or what we
call south and they move all the way
around in every single magnet
there are 16
counter-rotating vortexes of of energy
that all have different properties
involved
literally on the workbench
i
don't know why i didn't think about this
before i just barely thought about this
as illustration this we could take a
piece of steel a round piece of steel
and set it down there on the workbench
and find the right interchange of
magnetism
right interchange of fields right there
and we can
push
that that interchange into that iron bar
and instead of that iron bar leaping to
the magnet it'll try and get away as
fast as it can
because different fields interact with
different materials in different ways
okay this is the true nature of
magnetism we we're just barely just
cutting the cutting the edge or cut uh
cutting our teeth on exploring this
because there's so many permutations and
so much stuff some some will some will
pull into different some will pull into
steel some will pull into iron some will
repel iron we could we can levitate
things with the magnets now because we
find the right fields and the right
interactions to make it make it happen
so
that is the true nature of a magnetic
field
all right moving right along
it's in my lab
it's in my lab it's sitting on the shelf
we haven't
published anything out it's not it's not
public knowledge you guys are actually
hearing most of this
for the very first time except for some
of the people that have been uh in in
the in the dinners okay you're not going
to find 99 of this on the lab wait where
why are we here
okay
all right so you've seen the fields
you've now seen them moving you've now
seen them you've now seen the motion
that happens inside of a magnetic inside
of a magnet
can we go back to the one right before
this
ah thank you you've seen you've seen
these these fields now now what's really
going on here let's talk a little bit
about what is really going on oh this by
the way all this work is done by my
friend john de pew this artwork is
absolutely beautiful he's the foremost
expert on the true nature of magnetic
fields in the world no one else has got
it he and he's got some great stuff here
um
so we're going to talk a little bit
about the etheric field now all of these
points where these things cross
are actually where the ether energy is
tying into this reality and so if we can
create a a big enough field out here
we can
superimpose this we can superimpose
whatever is going on in there
on something outside so with that in
mind how many of you guys want to see an
actual over unity device
now um well almost everybody's raising
their hands everybody who didn't raise
their hand leaf
here's the deal
i said last year that
with the with the with the energies that
we're working with and the energies that
are that are that are coming out
that we are experiencing now um we need
an entirely new set of technologies
to be able to utilize them we're not
going to have the toasters that you plug
into the wall and stuff like that we
will have those in the interim but but
we need a new set of technologies and
this technology that you just saw a
little bit of and what i'm about to show
you is an entirely different way of
thinking about power generation and
power utilization so what we're going to
do is we're going to create a field
me a field
of energy
a field of light and information that
travels out and imbues itself like i
talked about earlier with the fractal
imaging imbues itself through implosion
on everything else around it so now we
can go forward please that is what i
want you to think about as you watch
this video
and you can see all this on his website
but it's uh
it it's not explained like this here
these are little mag are little pieces
of steel with magnets on them and
they're all spinning at the same time it
takes one watt of power to turn the
first one
and once the first one's turning you can
turn
i counted them out there's there's uh
like over 29 of them right here okay
that's not 29 over unity that's 29 times
over unity
all right
every single one of those can and has
been hooked up to fans
they're hooked up to
little uh uh power takeoff devices but
you're not going to get power by
sticking a sticking a coil next to this
like a bedini motor or something like
that
got to think differently got to think in
an entirely different mode of thinking
in order to in order to take power off
of these little things as soon as you
start messing around with them they
start having interesting characteristics
now what's what's really fun is that
these things can be any size as long as
they are perfectly matched with the
original one that's turning
it's off on the side you can't see it
because we don't want to show how i'm
sorry i just can't
but it's not one of these things that's
going to be oh it's going to be
suppressed to put no this is going to be
emerging technology in the next few
years we're not trying to revolutionize
the world destroy the oil industry get
rid of all power plants we're not trying
to do that because that's
i don't know doesn't work that way
but you're going to see super efficient
motors
you're going to see magnetic
communication because we've already
we've already played around with this
you can communicate through these things
once you create that etheric field you
know that that little squiggly thing
that i showed you
that field communicates to every single
one that you put into it
and so if you put your self into it
interesting things happen if you put
communication devices into it
interesting things happen so we're going
to be seeing this as emergent technology
we've already talked about heart mueller
and the global scaling this is what this
is this supplies itself to that that
idea it's done differently but that's
okay there's there's thousands of ways
to do something every road leads to rome
okay
what's up
they're on top of little glass bowls the
interesting thing is when we were doing
a
magnetic motor research
we looked at the way most magnetic
motors are designed and they're designed
all wrong
because
let me ask you this is there anything in
nature that is perfectly spherical raise
your hand if you can name one thing
that's perfectly spherical besides maybe
a buckyball
what
okay all right but is a bubble going to
remain perfectly spherical all the time
no it's moved by every little breath of
wind that moves around that pushes it
around
is there anything in nature that moves
perfectly circular
no
you get out into space
every single orbit of every single
planet is not circular it's elliptical
yes and that and and that we will be
talking about that because that is a
transitional phase we can put mercury
into we can put mercury into a
weightless space and then it will freeze
eventually and that that's basically a
transitional state we can do the same
thing with metals if they if they take
and put um if they take and melt metal
in space this is some of the experiments
that came out of skylab if you melt
metal in space
in a vacuum and allow it to solidify you
get ball bearings that have absolutely
no friction whatsoever because they have
no tool marks they have nothing there
yes
do electrons actually move around the
nucleus
i know that's that's the problem quantum
physics says that
okay our little our established idea
that electrons all right let's call that
q let's call that the nucleus and
electrons move in a uh this is the model
that we've all been taught electrons
move in a circular orbit and some of
them are moving this way and and
different and they move it in different
ways and patterns and at different
levels but as as uh
thurston lugwig said today with with uh
heisenberg's idea is that you can never
predict where that that uh electron is
going to be
it might be there or might be there it
might be there there are only
possibilities
so we don't really know what's going on
inside that electron but we use this
model
and that gives us a certain perspective
now in my article for the test the
technology or
the magazine anyway
i said something uh i said something
very poignant
something viewed from one perspective is
by definition two-dimensional do we live
in a two-dimensional world
no we don't we live in a three or four
or five-dimensional world and so we have
to look at things from many perspectives
science is one perspective
right here today is another perspective
so we're having fun with
that you suggesting that magnetic motors
need to be designed
we've already designed magnetic motors
with elliptical paths you send them down
a curved a long curve here and whip them
around and they'll send down the long
curve here and whip them around and send
down a long curve there and we can you
know do magnetic trains all day long
because they're moving in a linear
motion when you put magnets and i'm not
saying it's not possible because
this year i have seen some things that i
thought were not possible
last year
but when you put magnets into a sphere
do i have a sphere i don't have a sphere
if you put magnets into a circle in a
circular pattern it doesn't matter if
you've got
four magnets 20 feet apart or a hundred
magnets this far apart
they phase lock together and they create
different characteristics than the
individual magnet if magnets were a
static thing we could do amazing things
with it but they're not well
we could do certain things with it but
they're not you put them together and
they lock together and then and you
can't use them the same way anymore
so they can they can take magnets and
and add them together and it's the
gestalt the the hole is greater than the
sum of its parts
so yes
magnets magnetic motors circular they're
tough to make work i'm not saying it's
impossible i've heard some people that
have done it i'd really like to see it
but we've been playing with the
elliptical and that's great we've also
been playing with linear forget why you
know we can do it steam engines push
pull push pull push pull implosion
explosion implosion explosion and that
works great too and i just heard about
another one that uses that uses the the
nature of magnetism that that can move
apart and that and works on that
principle as well
don't limit yourself to one mode of
thinking we got the two-dimensional
perspective who wants to live on a piece
of paper it doesn't work
so
moving right along
what is next anyway
i'm not moving forward okay thanks
all right thank you we're going to move
on a little bit right now and study
about the true nature of electricity
and implosion
now we've always been taught
that in an electrical circuit you have a
battery
and that is going to push electrons
through the circuit over here through
the light bulb where it will generate
light lose a certain certain amount of
power and then come over here and drain
the battery and equalize let's equalize
the battery okay it's going to equalize
it we have a differential
push it over here and suddenly we have
an equalization no more power
well
quantum physics conventional quantum
physics has now learned that this is a
complete and utter fallacy
this has gotten us so far and we have
great flashlights and we have laser leds
and we have stuff like that but how do
we get to the next level we have to look
at it from another perspective and what
quantum physics says
is that there is a field
a field tracing
around this circuit a field that
surrounds everywhere
can i get some water
water
no water
yeah thank you
we we have a field around this circuit
and when we
put the battery when we put the final
components in line with that feel or
assuming in
into into a circuit
that
energy then collapses into the circuit
and manifests whatever the circuit is
designed to do
so the field is out here all the time
when we put that final when we throw
that switch when we put that final
component into place
the field then collapses and becomes
whatever we want it to be
all right so think about that the the
applications for this are you know when
you think backwards it's it's a little
bit different it's a little bit
different so we're not just generating
light coming off of here we're allowing
the ether to flow in a pattern that
allows the ether to manifest as light
unfortunately it also manifests as heat
which is loss well is heat loss no it's
a transitional phase of energy
differentials
all right
and to actually look at what those
fields are doing in there we look at
this this is a picture
of the energy that is traveling through
that wire
now one
pole of energy will start at one end and
move through that wire this way another
pull of energy will start at the other
end and move this way
and so where's the ether here
the ether is manifest at these points
there is no dc this is a this is a this
is a this is a battery voltage circuit
and it's alternating the entire time
somebody mentioned last night that in a
that in a straight piece of wire they
found that it had what .06 micro henrys
i think it was
six and six micro henrys thank you six
micro henries of inductance in a single
wire but wait a minute it's just a
single wire it's dc it's traveling
straight we shouldn't have any henry we
shouldn't have any inductance at all but
we do
because the energy is moving in this
pattern
this is why people when up when
you put uh when you put
excuse me wires together in a in a motor
or in a coil or something like that and
you start pumping energy through you
start getting heat and you start getting
problems and i figured out why it's gen
doing that i'll talk to you about it
today later tonight because there i
figured i i remembered something that
tells me why it's happening
the circle that's the uh
i'm sorry that that's an overlap that's
an artistic uh that's a that's an
artistic play right there
that's my buddy john de pew he's an
artist and uh yes
those circles are little curly cues and
they may actually be something because
nothing here is nothing here is
completely uh
uh
you know
just for looks but but we don't know yet
this is this is a field of study that
we're just we're just barely scratching
the surface on but we're working as fast
as we can now this this technology or
this this idea applied to things like
hydrogen generation
gives you a completely different
perspective on what's happening there so
you get a hydrogen you get a hydrogen
electrolyzer and you get a plate here
and a plate here and a plate here and
we're going to push a whole bunch of
electricity through this we're going to
generate heat and stuff like that but
what if we were to place the plates
right there excuse me my hands are
shaking what if we were to place the
plates right there on those zero point
spots
and where the two energies mix is the
space in between the plates and you
allow the etheric um or assuming you
allow the the etheric implosion to do
its work or you offset it so that the
plates are here and the conjunction is
there what's going to happen
no this is just straight dc
we don't are
being not being dc this is just straight
battery voltage
but using this
technique applied to a few applied to
some interesting things we've got 180
percent efficiency on electrolysis using
straight battery voltage
no frequencies not needed i mean
frequencies make it better but that's
okay yes
he was first
say again is it possible
um
we are working on measuring the position
sorry he asked is it possible to to
calculate the position of the nodes and
antinodes on an electric an electrical
wire um and the answer is
i don't know if i'm actually trying to
calculate it we're trying to measure it
out okay but yes it is it is possible
and what's interesting is those nodes
change by the amount of energy going
through it
and the um and the
the voltage and the current going
through it they stretch out elongate
stuff like that so okay what techniques
do you use to measure those because for
example in a bronze gas thing that's out
there
they say we're driving this and driving
this and all kinds of plates in the
middle that aren't driven
and that's striking a resonant cord with
what i'm seeing there in the coral
castle thing
um
i will i will talk to you about that
later okay
all right um let's see because we've got
a lot i've got a little bit more to go
through here let's see
uh the serial disk the the magnetic
levitating disk
yes it does and it's my personal belief
uh cyril had some amazing did some
amazing work with uh with magnetism and
levitating discs rotating magnets it is
my personal belief that
you can
we we've seen levitation with magnetism
already we've seen gravity negation with
magnetism already
if you combine it in certain patterns in
certain ways yes i believe that you
could lift it up and i believe that he
did it but that later on he was using
different types of magnets made with
different machines made in different
locations and every time you do every
time you change the parameters you
change the magnetic fields we're not
just dealing with north and south we're
dealing with many different fields so
thank you yes so it's my belief that it
worked in the beginning at least but
then as as the parameters changed things
changed from there so where are we here
okay this is this is a a graphic
representation of what's happening in
that wire it's a two dimensional
representation but you can see they the
the counter rotating spirals move
through the wire if you stack up a wire
in a coil and it's too close together
you'll generate heat it's not so much
separating them out so you get air
through it
to dissipate the heat so you're
separating them out so they no longer
interchange with the next layer above it
and i actually saw a hieronymous device
recently there was a multiple multiple
coiled multiple layered device and he
knew this somehow
and he had his primary coil with coil
was a single wire
that was straight that moved past the
other coils and that induced a field
from those spikes into the rest of the
coils and that gave him that gave him
some type of etheric energy that he was
able to tie into the radionically
you know we're not going to go into this
this uh because that's just too much to
go into right now this right here is um
a way that you can tie into and change
the nature of the energy that's flowing
in a circuit it's a spark gap
and when you when you have a pointed
spark gap you have a different
interaction of the these fields of
energy here these fields of light and
information that come off when you have
a square one you have a an entirely
different reaction here so if you're
working with tesla coils you're working
with radionics devices anything involves
the spark gap
change the length change the shape
change the material and you will change
the characteristics sunny ward he uses
that deal and he can implode anything
there you use a different shaped
electrode and you have different
responses
so moving right along
now i talked about collapsing energy
patterns
and
excuse me these these cr these
geometrical patterns here all do
different things and i'm not just
talking about pyramid power isn't that a
beautiful pyramid love to visit there
someday um i'm not just talking about
pyramid power preserving things uh
preserving uh preserving mummification
whatever i'm talking about actual energy
now tracy and i have a friend a little
guy named kwaku he said
a pyramid
he figured that a pyramid was a means of
controlling the energy and he wanted to
see what would happen if he just
let it just let it free-flow into
something and see what happened so he
made a whole bunch of little cones and i
started applying high voltage
electricity to it and what happened was
this beautiful
blue dna rope that came off of the top
of the cone now everybody's seen the
picture of the tesla coil inside the
pyramid
and you see the single thing going up
in the carillion photography this didn't
need for carillion photography this was
right there it was a it was energy
coming off the top of the cone so then
kwaku says hey wait a minute let's take
two cones and put them together we're
going to insulate them here and join
them together in a certain way using a
certain type of energy
and see what happens and so then he
takes a i'm sorry he applied 13 000
volts from a from a flyback transformer
on a television set to this and that's
how he saw the blue
the blue energy coming off of that but
what was interesting he said he measured
there and it was 13 000 volts he majored
there and it was 13 000 volts but
somehow this focused that energy and saw
the blue dna rope coming off so then as
i said he said let's put another one
down here let's put another one on there
we're going to join it together we're
going to input energy into it
and then we're going to put 13 000 volts
there and guess what happened
he sees a powerful this this one this
was this was insane because when we just
saw this it was uh scary
powerful white light coming off of this
thing it was like a white
it was like a it was like an etheric
light right there it was white and it
was just and it was silent it was very
strange
but when
the probe measured here measured 13 000
volts the probe moved up there
the probe shorted out and electrocuted
him
and crawled all over the insulation and
right into his hands and he had to jerk
it away because it was drawing him in
just from applying
two cones
and two neodymium magnets in the base
all right what's up
that was yours these were the uh these
the ones that you saw the blue one the
blue one the blue one was covered with
magnetite this one was just a straight
metallic cone
two metallic cones
yeah but here's the deal they have to be
specifically shaped here it's all fire
harmonically tuned if you just go out
and build a 45 degree cone not going to
do it it's got to be far harmonically
tuned
what's that
they are
they they had a plexiglas insulation
between between the bases
and they were held together with
magnetic fields so moving right along
how much time do we have
10 minutes is that what you said
who wants me to stop
one minute one minute okay we got one
minute all right
we're gonna warp time here
implosion is the secret to alchemy you
can change the nature of reality using
implosion
you can change the nature of reality
using your hands and implosion we've
been working with this uh
it's it's an amazing field you can
change the nature of reality with
implosion these are chhlodney patterns
cymatics patterns
all right these are little uh uh
egyptian pictograms and what's
interesting here is you see these little
wave patterns out here i've seen other
ones that look just like phonographs i
mean they look literally like
phonographs and these snakes are coming
out like sound wood and they've got
these old cylinders at the bottom is
that much of a stretch to think that
maybe the egyptians had you know uh like
like phonographic technology is really
easy to do
i mean it's it's not a straight it's not
a stretch at all for me to think that
but um then i started studying alchemy i
noticed that these eggs had these these
these same snakes and i can show you the
same thing in egyptian uh petroglyphs
these eggs have the same shapes with the
uh
with the um excuse me the snake wrapped
around it the same snake that's coming
out of there and so i said okay well
these patterns these beautiful
geometrical patterns play the created
from frequencies
come out of just vibrating sand or light
with with frequencies so what would
happen if you applied frequency to a
egg structure now i said last year
remember what this is this is the uh
this is the alchemist
alchemists and athor this is how they
changed lead into gold and different
stuff to make people immortal okay
what
what if you were able to play
frequencies through that would you
change the nature of the reality inside
of that egg
absolutely and people have done this now
and a friend of mine was involved in
experiment not exactly like this but
that used implosion and light and he was
able to make copper that didn't melt at
5000 degrees and wasn't touched by
nitric acid
and another person was doing the same
thing from a different angle and he was
able to make silver that isn't dissolved
by nitric acid and behaves more like
platinum but it's still x-rays out as us
as silver so we're changing the nature
of reality and it's all done with
implosion
so
that would be really really nice and i'm
looking forward to it i haven't done it
so
that would be great that would be
absolutely great
all right we're done there we're done
there how many how many minutes do you
need to really do a good job of
finishing up well i i'm just about there
okay i'm not going to talk about
i'm not going to talk about implosion in
the body just know that your bodies are
etheric devices that gather
the etheric energy and focus it in and
change it and you to utilize it okay you
can change it with your hands you can
change it with with your cellular
structure tracy talked about lyme's
disease she and i've had many
discussions about how the different
different what's up
that was when you were sleeping through
my talk
oh that's right yeah
okay um
your body has changed things inside of
itself and i've got i've got papers i
can show you out in the hall that
literally show that your body utilizes
etheric energy and changes the elements
back and forth inside inside your body
and without it okay these are actually
pictures of high voltage electrical
streams get with me outside and i will
show you the exact same thing inside of
your body and it's a plosive reaction
so think about that as we go into as you
go about your daily life and about how
you're tying in oh and about the lyme's
disease
different diseases limit your body's
ability to
implode and alchemically change to what
needs to be so
now we don't have time to go into that i
thought it was going to be much more
anyway
any questions right now
we've got one right here
okay
oh i'm sorry
i was curious if the
motion of electrons along the conductor
in the dc current had anything to do
with the patterns
oh absolutely absolutely if you want
something to flow do you call an
electrician or do you call a plumber
all right electricity travels on the
outside of the wire in those patterns
that i that i showed on the screen in
two counter rotating vortexes down the
length of the wire on the around the
outside
okay next question
what's that is that yeah wow
all right oh look there's one we'll do
one we'll do one more who who do you
recognize uh gentleman right there
it's okay can you just shout it out oh
okay oh yeah
i was just wondering if you could tell
you saw the uh the recent organic
machines that john deputy had made use
the mic
i can't no don't worry about i can't
talk about that i'm sorry i really am i
can't all right so don't worry about
that
when you when when the mother we call it
the mothership when when the mothership
has started up
spinning at a certain frequency they all
have a certain frequency
then you can start the next one you can
the next satellite spinning and the next
satellite spinning and the next
satellite spinning and they are tying
into that field that the first one
generates they're all tying together
and so you can put as many as you want
to into that field and they will all be
phase locked together
at that frequency at that rotational
pattern
you put power to one and the rest are
spinning
so
there yes it is magnetic frequency it is
magnetic frequency involved there
so
thank you very much i hope i made some
sense um
thanks a lot thank you vernon ross
okay